誒。
主席。
There are chapter one.
The committee today table.
或， irregularities，或shortcomings。
on behalf of the public accounts committee.
Mr. Secretary for Transport and Housing in Samcheol.
我有榮耀表達，我報告號碼六十九，今天。
Out of the nine chapters covered by the directors of audit report number 69.
我現在宣佈休會。本會現在舉行二零一八年二月七日嘅立法會例行會議。
委員會已決定舉行聽證會，就兩章節，內所含較嚴重的指控。
發言，石禮謙議員就政府賬目委員會第六十九號報告書向本會發言，石禮謙議員。
委員會對這些回覆滿意，並決定無公開聽證會於這些章節是必要的。
On administration of lump sum grants by the social welfare department, and Chapter Two on the procurement and maintenance of government vessels.
Would like to take this opportunity to express our appreciation to this bureau and departments in providing detailed replies to our questions.
委員會也研究了其他七章，由相關部門和機構提供書面回覆，回答成員的質疑，就他們如何應對審計署報告中提出的不足之處。
主席。
bureau for that.
我會 now report on the conclusions.
pending the finalisation of the review of the.
Some four to six years after funding approval.
Recommendation on the chapter on procurement and maintenance of government vessels.
委員會，尤其表達深切嘔心，和驚訝，關於貧。
It's said that the secretary of the transport and housing is not here, for he was the supervising.
委員會已決定舉行進一步聽證會，並延遲一份有關此議題的完整報告。
covers our conclusions and recommendations on the chapter on procurement and maintenance of government vessels only.
Effectiveness, in particular, for the Discipline Services Department to carry out law enforcement and emergency duties.
In view of the number and complexity of issues raised in the chapter on administration of lump sum grants by the social welfare department, supervised by the social welfare bureau.
judgement of marine department and the inexplicable decision in suspending the processing of vessels procurement projects for 35 months from December 2009 to October 2012.
The committee expresses alarm and finds it unacceptable that the marine department had failed to fulfil its duty in providing effective and timely government vessel procurement service for the user departments.
This。
在2014。
Marking scheme for the tender assessment.
The case only came to light, Mr. President.
委員會也表達深切 concern。
In this connection, the committee finds it appalling.
不acceptable about the deficiency in the marine department maintenance term contract management mechanism.
委員會指出，此決定在中止船隻採購項目，導致採購新船隻嚴重延宕。
The average ages of the four major classes of government vessels have increased significantly in the past 10 years as a result of such delay.
MD's performance in implementing new vessels recruitment projects, and step up its supervisory role to proactively identify problems faced by the marine department.
This was reviewed by a case of long outstanding payment of 1.68 million dollars for 98 works item carried out between 2010 to 2014.
Performance monitoring role effectively in the present case of the Marine Department implementation of vessels procurement projects. It's sad that he is not here. He should have learned more. The Transport and Housing Bureau is urged to closely monitor.
The delay for this 1.68 million was caused by the subject inspector who did not obtain approval for the job orders and did not submit relevant invoices to the Marine Department Accounting Services Section for processing.
In turn, call for more preventive maintenance and incur extra maintenance costs and downtime for the vessels. As a result, the user department's operation safety, efficiency and effectiveness have adversely been affected.
委員會已研究其他與提供維護服務有關的議題，包括海事部門的不足，包括報告船舶可用率的不足，以及從預購維護期合約中獲得的有限競爭。
The marine department is responsible for the procurement of new vessels as well as their maintenance for 14 government departments, including five discipline services departments. The vessels are essential for the department's operation, safety, efficiency.
Among the 25 ongoing vessel projects, 12 of them, Mr. President, have experienced delays, including five projects which have missed their target vessel delivery dates by five months to four years, and seven projects which were still in tender shipbuilding stage.
That the transport and housing bureau, Mr. Secretary in absentia, as the bureau overseeing the operation of the marine department, as in other cases previously investigated by the committees on department under its supervision, have failed again to perform.
當啲合約要續簽。
質詢底下質詢，林卓廷議員。
lastly, I like to record my appreciation.
委員會 notes that the marine department have taken various measures to enhance the management of TOEUM contracts.
Of the contribution made by members of this committee, our gratitude goes to the witnesses who attended the hearings. I would also like to express.
Our gratitude to the director of audit and his colleagues for their unfailing support, and last but not least to our secretary for their unfailing support too. Thank you.